<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tabula Rasa</title>
    <link>https://atkinew0.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tabula Rasa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 20:09:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://atkinew0.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://atkinew0.github.io/projects/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 20:09:16 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkinew0.github.io/projects/projects/</guid>
      <description>.project-container{ display:flex; margin:50px; } .project-image { width:80%; height:80%; box-sizing:border-box; } .project-image:hover{ border:red solid 3px; } .label{ text-align:center; font-weight:bold; }  These are some of the projects I have made to learn programming concepts: Mastershell   JSQuiz</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eli Atkinson</title>
      <link>https://atkinew0.github.io/about-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 21:24:33 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkinew0.github.io/about-hugo/</guid>
      <description>I am a lawyer, programmer and foreign language learner (Japanese, Spanish, French, and a little Russian and Chinese). I plan to write about my thoughts and projects making automated tools to learn programming languages, and whatever else pops into my head. Contact me at atkinson.eli@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Language Learning Applied To Programming</title>
      <link>https://atkinew0.github.io/posts/a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 21:03:12 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkinew0.github.io/posts/a/</guid>
      <description>Studying and using foreign languages for most of my career may have skewed the lense I look at learning anything through, but I often wonder if programmers, who frequently find themselves having to learn new programming languages and concepts could benefit from many techniques and methods developed for second language acquisition. I plan to explore tools and ideas for making learning programming easier in this series of posts.
One objection that I imagine many programmers might have to the suggestion that learning programming should be anything like learning a second language is that learning programming is primarily about understanding the concepts whereas language learning is more about rote memorization of vocabulary items.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>